const questions = [
	{
		question: "What is the full meaning HTML",
		options: [
			"High Text Mosaic Language",
			"Hyper Text Markup Language",
			"An english language",
			"A language",
		],
		correct: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
		id: 1,
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which of the following function of Array object removes the first element from an array and return that element",
		options: ["reverse()", "shift()", "slice()", "some()"],
		correct: "shift()",
		id: 2,
	},
	{
		question: "const arr = [1,2,3] '\n' arr.pop()",
		options: ["0", "2", "1", "3"],
		correct: "3",
		id: 3,
	},
	{
		question: "What is '||' in Javascript",
		options: ["and", "either", "with", "or"],
		correct: "or",
		id: 4,
	},
	{
		question: "What is the full meaning of NPM?",
		options: [
			"Node Package Manager",
			"Nano Particle Motion",
			"Node Plugin Manager",
			"Node Package Mongo",
		],
		correct: "Node Package Manager",
		id: 5,
	},
	{
		question: "The following are asynchronous programming concepts except",
		options: ["callbacks", "fufil", "Promises", "async/await"],
		correct: "Fufil",
		id: 6,
	},
	{
		question: "Which of the following is not a reserved word in JavaScript",
		options: ["interface", "throws", "program", "short"],
		correct: "program",
		id: 7,
	},
	{
		question:
			"What is the method in JavaScript used to remove the whitespace at the beginning and end of any string",
		options: ["strip()", "trim()", "stripped()", "trimmed()"],
		correct: "trim()",
		id: 8,
	},
	{
		question:
			"In JavaScript,we do not have datatypes like integer and float. What is the function that can be used to check if the number is an integer or not?",
		options: [
			"Integer(value)",
			"ifInteger(value)",
			"isInteger(value)",
			"forInteger",
		],
		correct: "isInteger(value)",
		id: 9,
	},

	{
		question: "Which of the following is an advantage of using JavaScript",
		options: [
			"Increased Interactivity",
			"Less server interaction",
			"Immediate feedback from the users",
			"All of the above",
		],
		correct: "All of the above",
		id: 10,
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which function of an Array object calls a function for each element in the array",
		options: ["forEach()", "every()", "forEvery()", "each()"],
		correct: "forEach()",
		id: 11,
	},
	{
		question: "JavaScript is _______ language.",
		options: ["a compiled", "an interpreted"],
		correct: "an interpreted",
		id: 12,
	},
	{
		question: "Which was the first browser to support JavaScript",
		options: ["Mozilla Firefox", "Netscape", "Google Chrome", "IE"],
		correct: "Netscape",
		id: 13,
	},
	{
		question: "The following are array methods except",
		options: ["pop()", "has()", "some()", "shift()"],
		correct: "has()",
		id: 14,
	},
	{
		question: "Which of the following is a JavaScript runtime environment",
		options: ["Node.js", "Deno", "All of the above", "None of the above"],
		correct: "All of the above",
		id: 15,
	},
];
export default questions;
